http://www.tornadogames.com/privacy.phtml

Free Mobile Apps, Free Online Games, Casual Games, Downloadable Computer Games, PC Games, Flash Games - Tornado Games
Play With Friends
Try our new game!Get it Free on your Mobile Device -> Keno - Tornado Games Style
Cheap Flights Explained - My wife and I have saved over $9,000 on flights in the last 2 years. In fact, all of our direct round trip flights have been $22.40 - that's for both tickets.
Click here to read how we did it - Cheap Flights Explained.
Search:
Privacy Policy
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site.
These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked
or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.
These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or
to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://networkadvertising.org
Tornadogames.com is committed to your privacy during the use of our
online site and games. We honor your privacy and at the same time we do
collect some information about the use of our site that helps us get a
better idea of what our users like and what they don't like. The information
we collect and analyze is very general and is not targeted at an individuals
usage but more of a broad scope of the type of actions taking place at
this domain. The "Privacy Policy" of this site may change at
any time so please check back often.
What do we require from you?
Nothing. No information is ever required by a user of tornadogames.com.
We do require an account setup (which is free) if you want to set high
scores or collect Tcaps for discounts on purchases. The account setup
process is not required by any user, it is an option to all players over
the age of 13. If you do setup an account the information supplied by
you may be disclosed to authorities if the question ever came up. We
will not willing hand over your information. If you do create an account
it is your responsibility to control the access to that account.
Sharing information?
We do not share any information you supply to us with anyone or company
that is not owned by Jetacer Interactive LLC unless required by law.
Cookies?
We do use cookies to track items like member login, shopping carts, dates
of events and other non-critical data. We do not store personal information
in the cookie format.
Consent.
By using tornadogames.com, you consent to all of the items listed
in this Privacy Policy. You also understand that this Privacy Policy can
change without notice.
Only This Site.
This privacy policy is only for tornadogames.com, if you leave this site
by means of a link or other method please know that you are no longer
protected by this Privacy Policy.
[Home]
[Games]
[Support]
[Link to Games]
[Submit Content]
[Custom Game & App Development]
[Search]
[Privacy Policy]
[Free games to download or post on your web site]
[Apps For Your Phone]
[Free Online Games]
[Puzzle Games]
[Sport Games]
[Board Games]
[Arcade Games]
[Card Games]
[Gambling Games]
